(Sheldon:)You heard him, Leonard.
(Sheldon:)No, it's not racist.
(Howard:)Are we sure this is the place?
(Raj:)The doorman said this
is the right building.
(Leonard:)I think if you're pulling up
your pants,
(Leonard:)you're not a doorman.
MAN:
Who is it?
Uh, I'm looking
for a Professor Sharpe?
(Prof Sharpe:)Hold on.
(Prof Sharpe:)Can I help you?
Hi.
(Leonard:)We're from the university. We're
trying to get some information
(Leonard:)about Professor Abbott.
(Howard:)We were cleaning
out his office
(Howard:)and found these books
full of numbers.
(Leonard:)Any chance you
know what it is?
(Prof Sharpe:)Yes, he was always
working on this.
Oh.
(Amy:)I was thinking
it might be
(Raj:)some sort of interstellar
coordinate system,
(Raj:)maybe an updated version
of Hubble's law.
(Raj:)I keep seeing the
number 90 repeating.
(Raj:)That could be the angle
of perturbation
(Raj:)of a distant galaxy.
(Prof Sharpe:)It's the number
of calories in a yogurt.
(Prof Sharpe:)That's his food diary.
(Leonard:)Really?
(Prof Sharpe:)Yeah, he wrote down
everything he ever ate.